We'll be right back.
The End of the Legendary Man, the day the C-Train cried.
Pleased to meet you, Your Honor.
My name is Spandum.
I'm with CP5.
A pleasure.
And thanks.
You saved us.
We can take over the investigation from here if you don't mind.
We'll give them a full interrogation.
Hmm.
Just try talking your way out of this one.
The trust they had in you has been shattered.
Soon those blueprints for the ancient weapons will be mine.
How could this happen?
First off, about the C-Train.
Magnificent work.
With its help, Water 7 will continue to grow and flourish.
For that, on the previous charge of building Gold Rogers' ship, your acquittal today had
pretty much already been decided.
Knowing that, why in the world would you commit such a heinous crime and erase that opportunity?
Please, explain yourself.
That's a lie!
It wasn't Tom or any of us that attacked the judicial ship.
It was that idiot Spandum!
He's the one responsible!
Ha ha ha!
Sure it was!
He's not serious, is he?
What kind of crap is he trying to pull?
Why would a government agency like CP5 attack a judicial ship?
There's no way!
You're gonna have to come up with a better lie than that, Mr. Apprentice.
Ha ha ha ha!
Your name is Cutty Flam, correct?
I believe that was the name we took down from you when we caught you red-handed on board
one of those treacherous raid ships.
And correct me if I'm mistaken, but weren't those very same raid ships all made by your company?
Ships that would do such a horrible thing.
Something so awful are no longer my ships!
Tom, pour off his chains!
He's on a rampage!
Take aim!
He just hit him.
Tom has never hit Frankie before.
What'd you do that for?
They're no longer your ships, huh?
Don't you ever say that again!
What's wrong with saying that?
I wish I'd never made them!
If those ships didn't exist, then nobody would have gotten hurt!
When a ship is built, no matter what type,
it's neither good nor evil.
I don't care what kind of ship you choose to make for the rest of your life.
Remember, even if the ships you build hurt someone,
even if they destroy the world,
even if no one else does,
their creator must love them unconditionally.
The one who made them must never deny them!
Don't place the blame on the ships!
You must be proud
of every ship you've ever created!
I'm dead!
Papa!
Iceberg.
Frankie.
Whatever happens,
don't interfere with what I'm about to do.
No matter what.
It's the world government who pinned this crime on us,
and it's the world government who will be the ones to judge it.
There's no way for us to be cleared of these charges.
It's over.
It must be tough for you to see your innocent ships
being used for something as horrible as this.
I bet you really want to hit that guy.
Don't you, Frankie?
Frankie.
What are you doing?
He's going crazy again.
What is he doing?
Stop it, please.
You're making things worse than they already are.
Can you even comprehend
the pain that you put that boy through?
Fire!
They shot him.
Tom, no!
Tranquilizers, huh?
Not so tough now, are you?
Serves you right, fish man!
Tom, wait!
Why are you doing this?
What are you standing around for?
Get over there and apprehend them!
We're going to take Tom
and every last one of his villainous workers
down to Ellie's lobby!
Who would have thought that Tom
could be such a dangerous guy?
What the hell was he thinking?
Just what you'd expect
from a man who sold his soul to pirates!
He made those battleships
and waited around for a chance like this
to use them!
How dare you talk about him like that,
you bastards!
Stop it!
It's all right.
Tom!
I'd like to confess.
Hmm?
The raid on the judicial ship
was led by me.
That's not true!
Why would you say that?
But I have a request.
Save your breath, fish man!
Nobody gives a damn about your...
Shut your mouth, CP-5!
So, what is this request?
If building the sea train
was supposed to be considered a pardon
for one charge against me,
then I'd like to be pardoned
for today's charges.
Huh?
Even if that request is granted,
you'll be right back
to where you were to begin with.
With the charge of building a ship
for the King of the Pirates,
which will result in the maximum penalty.
Sounds good.
I like that better anyway.
Giving a hand to that Roger guy
is something I'll never forget.
In fact,
it's something I take great pride in!
He's proud of that?
I can't believe he'd make such a bold claim
about something so despicable.
Traitor!
Fish man!
You regret that!
Why, Tom?
Tell me!
It's for the best.
Now, listen.
Don't blame yourself for this.
I never thought the world government
would go to such extremes
to get the blueprints.
And the situation with Roger
only makes the matter worse.
Even so,
it doesn't have to be this way!
No, it's fine.
Look around you.
Even if I'm charged with a crime
from 14 years ago,
nothing else about this town
is the same now
as it was back then.
This island is alive
and strong.
Tom, this is only the beginning.
No matter what ends up
happening to me,
I was still able
to help this town.
My dream
has finally
begun to run.
Tom, don't please!
Tom, no!
Iceberg.
Frankie.
Take care of the blueprints.
Kokoro.
Yokozuna.
Thank you
for everything.
The tranquilizers
finally kicked in!
Capture those three
for the judicial ship attack!
Yes, sir!
Hold it.
I'm amending the charges.
For the crime of designing
and building a ship
for Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
Tom and Tom alone
will be apprehended
and taken to Annie's lobby.
That is all.
What in the hell
got into that old
geezer's head?
Whatever.
I don't need his lackeys.
Release those two apprentices!
Tom can't be saved from this.
It's the government
we're up against.
There's nothing we can do.
Endure it.
Tom traded his life
for yours.
If you make them
your enemy,
you won't be able to win
no matter how many lives
you have to give.
Annie's lobby
is the government's
personal judicial island.
Not one single person
who's been sent
to that dreadful place
has ever been seen again.
The sea train
is ready for departure, sir.
We can leave
any time you like.
Very good.
Cocoa.
Ha ha!
Let's get moving, men.
Load up the prisoner.
I can't.
This bloated fish man
is going for
a little train ride.
Endure this!
Hey!
Stop it!
Get out of the way!
Oh!
Really messed up his face!
No!
Tom's apprentice
is the one on a rampage!
No!
Stop!
I'd better get him!
Capture that criminal!
The rest of you,
take Tom to the train!
That's not gonna happen!
Nobody's taking him anywhere!
Fire at will!
Tom's staying right here!
Are you okay?
After him!
Hurry!
Get out of here!
Fire!
Damn it!
He got away!
I'll get that cutty flam brat
if it's the last thing I do!
That little criminal
will pay for what he's done!
Mark my words,
once this case is over,
I'll have him sent to the gallows!
Spot him!
He's here!
Now!
It...
夢見た僕らは間違いじゃないと信じて 荒く埋れる海原を渡って行ける
誰よりも浮かんで 思いやりもあるけれど
もしも君がこの船を降りて 違う世界にいたとしても
最後にはきっと笑えるよ
ご視聴ありがとうございました
I've been looking forward to seeing you
Wait, is that you Spanda?
Spandam! Spandam! There's an M at the end!
Lucci, hurry up and bring them to Eni's lobby already
Yes, sir
Hey, hold on! Let him go!
What was that?
Uh, nothing, sorry
On the next, One Piece! The truth behind her betrayal!
Robin's sorrowful decision! I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
You're in between the shapes and 억破 but...
I need you to visit your auntie!
Do you see her?
Me.